[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the first man to complete one full orbit of the earth?",
   "Answer": "Yuri Gagarin"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "On which hemisphere were the most dinosaur skeletons found?",
   "Answer": "The northern hemisphere"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "What color is cobalt?",
   "Answer": "Blue"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "Who invented vulcanized rubber?",
   "Answer": "Charles Goodyear"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "What is the organ that is affected when one is suffering from hepatitis?",
   "Answer": "Liver"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "Which device do we use to look at the stars?",
   "Answer": "Telescope"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Which device is used to measure the air pressure?",
   "Answer": "Barometer"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "Which unit indicates the light intensity?",
   "Answer": "Candela"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the father of the atomic bomb?",
   "Answer": "Robert Oppenheimer"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "Who invented the barometer?",
   "Answer": "Torricelli"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the first American in space?",
   "Answer": "Alan Shepard"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "Two brothers invented the hot air balloon. What was their surname?",
   "Answer": "Montgolfier"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the inventor of the steam engine?",
   "Answer": "James Watt"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "Which device was invented by Henry Mill?",
   "Answer": "The typewriter"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "What is the lightest existing metal?",
   "Answer": "Lithium"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "What is the substance known by the chemical formula NH3?",
   "Answer": "Ammoniac"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "What is the process called when an atom splits?",
   "Answer": "Nuclear Fission"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "Who discoved one of the first antibiotics: penicillin?",
   "Answer": "Alexander Fleming"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "Which planet stays the closest to earth?",
   "Answer": "Mercury"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "What was the name of the first satellite in space?",
   "Answer": "Sputnik I"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "Which natural substance is the hardest?",
   "Answer": "Diamond"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "What is the lightest chemical element?",
   "Answer": "Hydrogen"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "What is the brightest star in the northern hemisphere?",
   "Answer": "Sirius"
 },
 {
   "No": 24,
   "Quiz question": "Which planet was discovered by Frederik Herschel in 1781?",
   "Answer": "Uranus"
 },
 {
   "No": 25,
   "Quiz question": "In astronomy, what are Pallas, Vesta and Davida?",
   "Answer": "Asteroids"
 },
 {
   "No": 26,
   "Quiz question": "How many kidneys does a normal person have?",
   "Answer": "Two kidneys"
 },
 {
   "No": 27,
   "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the Platinum element?",
   "Answer": "The symbol Pt"
 },
 {
   "No": 28,
   "Quiz question": "How many eyes does a honeybee have? One, four or five?",
   "Answer": "Five"
 },
 {
   "No": 29,
   "Quiz question": "What is the color of giraffe tongue",
   "Answer": "Blue/Purple"
 }
]
